<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MathApp</string>

    <string-array name="activities_list">
        <item>Introduction</item>
        <item>Numerical Representation</item>
        <item>Complex Plane</item>
        <item>Basic Operations</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="introduction_header">Introduction</string>
    <string name="introduction_body">What separates complex numbers from familiar numbers (the
        integers, the reals, etc.) is the declaration of a specific value <i>i</i> to represent the
        square root of negative one.\n\nWhen we use this <i>i</i> term, now we can factor <i>i</i> out
        of several questions that previously were "undefined", then continue evaluating them with
        familiar methods.\n\nThis isn\'t just a clever workaround, this actually leads to a
        mathematically correct framework where we can define numbers, operations, relationships, and
        all of the familiar mathematics, and methodically, repeatably arrive at the correct
        solutions to a diverse range of problems.  These solutions are even an essential
        "elementary" piece of most modern engineering, including electronics, physics, mechanical
        engineering, population modelling, and so forth.
    </string>
    <string name="numerical_representation_header">Numerical Representation</string>
    <string name="numerical_representation_body">There are two primary ways to represent a complex
        number.  The first, more intuitively, is a real component plus an imaginary component
        multiplied by <i>i</i>.  Alternatively, complex numbers can be represented in polar
        coordinates, with a scalar modulus times an argument (radian angle) relative to the real
        axis.
    </string>
    <string name="complex_roots_header">Complex Roots</string>
    <string name="complex_roots_body">For every non-zero complex number, there are guaranteed to be
        exactly <i>n</i> <i>n</i>-th roots.  For example, there are exactly 2 square roots of 1,
        3 cube roots, 7 7-th roots, and so on.\n\nOne neat thing to notice, if you look at them on
        the complex plane, they all fall on the same circle and are evenly spaced out.\n\nTo try
        this out, you can enter any complex number below and see the list of its roots.
    </string>
    <string name="cartesian_representation">Cartesian Representation</string>
    <string name="polar_representation">Polar Representation</string>
</resources>
